864-420-2756 - kevbost@gmail.com - kevbost.github.io

The Iron Yard Greenville : 2014

CodeLynx, Software Engineer : 2014-present

## **TOOLBOX**

Advanced: RWD, Advanced SASS, HTML5, GIT, Javascript, NodeJS, Gulp, UnderscoreJS, Bootstrap 4,

Sublime Text, Electron, VSCode, iTerm, ConEmu, ~/. zshrc, Markdown, Unix, VIM

**Experience:** Angular 1.x, Aurelia, Durandal/Knockout, Backbone, VersionOne, `\${ES2015}` **Working:** LESS, Electron, React, Meteor, Mongo/Mongoose, Functional JS, Razor, ASP.NET

Plus: Visual Studio 2015 TFS, RFID Integration, Unreal, Arduino, Spark/Particle

**Design:** Proficient in Adobe Photoshop, InDesign, Illustrator, Lightroom

Office: Experienced use of Microsoft Word, Excel, Outlook, Google Docs Suite, Enspire OS: Advanced control of OSX, Microsoft Windows 7. Working use of Debian, Fedora

## **PROFILE**

I am a programmer with 2 years of experience enthusiastically searching to find the best place for myself in the developers' work force. Successful problem solving drives my work and makes the challenge of coding enjoyable and exciting. I am inspired and ready to work hard with my colleagues to create user friendly and fun web experiences.

### **EXTRA**

CharlestonJS (MEETUP) — 2014-PRESENT Co-Founder, Organizer, Speaker

## **EXPERIENCE**

#### CODELYNX — 2014-PRESENT

Software Engineering - Full time UX/UI Engineer. Responsible for front-end build systems, package management, CSS (SCSS) Architecture & Composition, Full Project HTML System Standardization, JavaScript Framework Integration, View & ViewModel Composition & Styling, Technology Research [Animation, RFID, Barcode Parsing, Arduino Prototyping, Hardware Integration].

Responsible for UI/UX across all of our commercial projects, including 6 contracted applications, all pre/post-compiled HTML and SCSS assets, integration JavaScript frameworks and libraries. Hardware that needs to be configured, integrated, and documented. I am often able to bring what I discover in my many personal projects back to CodeLynx, of which they have been able to use to save development time and increase overall profit and value.

#### MITCHELL INDUSTRIAL CONTROLS — 2012-2014

Industrial Heating Solutions – I wore all hats at MICC, raw data entry, invoicing, mechanical drawing and physical measurement, order processing, purchasing, customer relations, product photography, industrial controller custom programming, inventory management, and shipping & receiving.

Having no prior experience with the company's technology and materials, I learned on the job. As a self-starter, am most proud of the work I did to revitalize and perfect the inventory management system. For the first time in 30+ years all inventory was/will be accounted for.

### GREENVILLE ORGANIC FOODS ORGANIZATION (GOFO) — 2010-2014

Community Education, Non Profit - Web maintenance / re-design / consultant, Promotional print media design, file system restructuring and relocation, marketing photographer.

I started my time at GOFO as a volunteer in their garden. Over 4 years, I photographed events, rebuilt their website, coached the early stages of their social media presence, designed two 20 page event brochures (which were used as templates for the following years' events), designed multiple runs of posters banners and postcards, restructured file system and transfer to the cloud managing permissions for a medium sized team.

# **EDUCATION**

#### THE IRON YARD -2014

The Iron Yard's Front End Web Design and Engineering program is a web development accelerator that prepares its students to enter the professional world as knowledgeable and confident programmers.

#### VIRGINIA INTERMONT COLLEGE — 2007-2010

Photography and Digital Imaging - Photographic theory and implementation, advanced darkroom knowledge, advanced Photoshop, advanced digital printing, photographic history, and design theory.